export const data =[
{
  question:"Which type of JavaScript language is...",
  option1:"Object-Oriented" ,
  option2:"Object-Based" ,
  option3:"Assembly-language" ,
  option4: "High-level",
  ans: 2,

},
{
    question:"Which one of the following also known as Conditional Expression:",
    option1:"Alternative to if-else",
    option2:"Switch statement" ,
    option3: "If-then-else statement",
    option4: "immediate if ",
    ans:4 ,
},
{
    question:"In JavaScript, what is a block of statement?",
    option1:"Conditional block" ,
    option2: "block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement",
    option3: "both conditional block and a single statement",
    option4:"block that contains a single statement" ,
    ans:2 ,
  
  },
  {
      question:"When interpreter encounters an empty statements, what it will do:",
      option1: "Shows a warning",
      option2: "Prompts to complete the statement",
      option3:"Throws an error" ,
      option4:"Ignores the statements" ,
      ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question:"The 'function' and 'var' are known as:",
    option1: "Keywords",
    option2: "Data types",
    option3:"Declaration statements" ,
    option4: "Prototypes",
    ans:3 ,
  
  },
  {
      question:"Which one of the following is the correct way for calling the JavaScript code?",
      option1:"Preprocessor",
      option2: "Triggering Event",
      option3: "RMI",
      option4: "Function/Method",
      ans: 4,
  },
  {
    question:"Which of the following type of a variable is volatile?",
    option1:"Mutable variable" ,
    option2: "Dynamic variable",
    option3: "Volatile variable",
    option4:"Immutable variable" ,
    ans:1 ,
  
  },
  {
      question:"Which of the following option is used as hexadecimal literal beginning?",
      option1: "00",
      option2:"0x" ,
      option3: "0X",
      option4: "Both 0x and 0X",
      ans:4 ,
  },
  {
    question:"In the JavaScript, which one of the following is not considered as an error:",
    option1: "Syntax error",
    option2:"Missing of semicolons" ,
    option3:"Division by zero" ,
    option4: "Missing of Bracket",
    ans: 3,
  
  },
  {
      question:" Which of the following number object function returns the value of the number?",
      option1: "toString()",
      option2:"valueOf()" ,
      option3:"toLocaleString()" ,
      option4: "toPrecision()",
      ans: 2,
  },
];